Preliminary Inventory to the Major General Mirovicz papers, 1914-1916
Hoover Institution Archives
Major General Mirovicz papers,
1914-1916
XX125
Mirovicz, Major General
1 folder, 1 envelope. (0.2 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Reports, orders, maps, and photographs, relating to military operations of the Second and Third Finland Rifle Brigades in four battles on the Riga Front and in the Carpathian Mountains.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
Russia.--Armiia.--Finliandskaia Strelkovaia Brigada, 2.; Russia.--Armiia.--Finliandskaia Strelkovaia Brigada, 3.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Campaigns--Eastern.; Russia.
Biography
Major general, Imperial Russian army.
Container List
- Opisanie diestvii 2-i Finlandskoi strielkovoi brigady w raionie Lyi-Avgustov s 24-go Avgusta po 2 Sentiabria 1914 goda (Box 1.)
- Opisanie destvii 2-i Finlandskoi strielkovoi brigady 13 Sentiabria po 28 Sentiabria (1914?)
- Same as above... 12-? Oktiabr' 1914... v bolakh pod Bakalarzhevym
- Same as above... ? Ianvar'-10 Febral' 1915 goda
- Two maps used in operations
- Miscellaneous army, division and brigade orders, 1915 December-1916 August, as follows:
  - ? Piekhotnoi divisii: Prikaz No. 75, 1915 December 1915
  - 3 Finlandskoi strielkovoi divisii: Prikaz No. 1, 25 Iul. 1916
  - 22 Korpus, Artilleriiskaia gruppa:
    - 17 Avgusta 1916: Prikaz No. 2
    - 20 Avgusta 1916: Prikaz No. 3
    - 2 Sentiabria 1916: Prikaz No. 5
  - 3 Finlandskoi strielkovoi divisii: Prikaz No. 20?, 1915 Dec. 16?
  - 22 Korpus Artillerii Inspektor. Prikaz No. 29 5 Sentiabria 1916
- Photo file, Five air photographs of the front